{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "Politics%3A%20US",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who%20was%20the%20first%20President%20of%20the%20United%20States%3F",
      "correct_answer": "George%20Washington",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Thomas%20Jefferson",
        "Abraham%20Lincoln",
        "John%20Adams"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Politics%3A%20US",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20maximum%20number%20of%20terms%20a%20President%20can%20serve%20in%20the%20United%20States%3F",
      "correct_answer": "2",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "1",
        "3",
        "Unlimited"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Politics%3A%20US",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who%20is%20the%20current%20Speaker%20of%20the%20United%20States%20House%20of%20Representatives%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Nancy%20Pelosi",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Chuck%20Schumer",
        "Mitch%20McConnell",
        "Kevin%20McCarthy"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Politics%3A%20US",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which%20political%20party%20is%20represented%20by%20the%20color%20red%20in%20the%20United%20States%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Republican%20Party",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Democratic%20Party",
        "Libertarian%20Party",
        "Green%20Party"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Politics%3A%20US",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "How%20many%20Senators%20are%20there%20in%20the%20United%20States%20Senate%3F",
      "correct_answer": "100",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "50",
        "200",
        "75"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Politics%3A%20US",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who%20is%20the%20current%20Vice%20President%20of%20the%20United%20States%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Kamala%20Harris",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Joe%20Biden",
        "Mike%20Pence",
        "Nancy%20Pelosi"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Politics%3A%20US",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which%20Amendment%20to%20the%20United%20States%20Constitution%20guarantees%20freedom%20of%20speech%3F",
      "correct_answer": "First",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Second",
        "Fourth",
        "Fifth"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Politics%3A%20US",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who%20is%20the%20current%20Secretary%20of%20State%20of%20the%20United%20States%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Antony%20Blinken",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Mike%20Pompeo",
        "Hillary%20Clinton",
        "John%20Kerry"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Politics%3A%20US",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20capital%20of%20the%20United%20States%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Washington%2C%20D.C.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "New%20York%20City%2C%20NY",
        "Los%20Angeles%2C%20CA",
        "Chicago%2C%20IL"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Politics%3A%20US",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who%20was%20the%20only%20US%20President%20to%20resign%20from%20office%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Richard%20Nixon",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "John%20F.%20Kennedy",
        "Jimmy%20Carter",
        "Bill%20Clinton"
      ]
    }
  ]
}
